123people.com 2013-06-22

# Privacy Policy | 123people.com

When you sign up for a user account or to use yelster's services, we may collect the following types of information:

**Actively provided data**

We collect and use personal information in accordance with the Austrian Data Protection Act (DSG 2000) limited to the technically necessary extent in order to be able to perform contractual obligations to the customer. 

In order to fulfill our contractual agreements, the data collected during the registration will be processed. These are (unless otherwise specified by you) your first and last name, e-mail address, telephone number and credit card information.

This data will be used only in connection with the performance of contractual obligations. We do not share your personal data with third parties. For the performance of the service a Safe Harbor certified service provider based in the USA, as well as EU-based service providers are applied.

Your specified e-mail address is used as the primary contact during our business relationship.

You agree to the use of your e-mail address for the purpose of sending you additional information about our services and promotions. If you do not wish to receive any more additional information via email, [feel free to contact us](https://www.123people.com/page/contact).

**Passively provided data**

**Cookies** \- When you visit our website, we send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people search. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. 

**Log information** \- When you use 123people services, our servers can automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request or one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

**User communications** \- When you send an email or other communication to us, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. These communications will be removed within the statutory period after the end of the customer relationship. 

**Affiliated sites** \- We offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to yelster in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.

**Links** \- yelster may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our search technology, customized content and advertising. 

**Other sites** \- This Privacy Policy applies to web sites and services that are owned and operated by yelster . We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. 

yelster processes personal information on our own servers in Austria and in other countries within the European Economic Area.
